翻译校对       Mam
日  听      マキ
日听校对       Syura
翻译        花解语
时间轴       鬼 忻奈
压制      娜夏
OP&ED       葉隠
Syura
诸神字幕组
Welcome!
いらっしゃいませ
"The Host Club is now open for...
business?"
My, what is that unfamiliar-
looking piece of furniture?
あら　この見慣れない家具は？
That is a kotatsu, if memory serves.
確か…コタツというものですわ
Oh, is that what those are?
It's my first time seeing one.
まぁ　これが…？
私　初めて目にしましたわ
Me, too.
私も
Normally, kotatsu are only
used during the winter.
本来コタツは冬と決まっています
As such, it may be a little
early in the season for these,
ですから　時期的には少々早いのですが
which makes this fitting for all of you,
季節の先取りこそ遊び上手な皆さんには相応しい
who are ahead of your time,
to take pleasure in.
Ladies, please fully enjoy
the home-style kotatsu service
皆様本日はわれらホスト部員とのコタツ団欒サービスを
of the Host Club members today.
存分にお楽しみください
Is sitting under a kotatsu
really all that fun?
そんなにコタツなんて面白いんですかね
They're a hit, aren't they?
受けてるだろ？
Is providing kotatsu service like this
one of Tamaki- senpai's ideas?
こういうコタツサービスとかも環先輩のアイディアなんですか
Yeah.
What's the matter?
Are you discontent with this?
どうした　何か不満でも？
I've always thought
it was pretty remarkable,
いつも不思議に思ってたんですけど
but Kyoya- senpai, the Host Club
was originally founded
そもそもこのホスト部って
環先輩と鏡夜先輩の二人で立ち上げたんですよね
by both you and Tamaki- senpai, right?
Yes, and?
そうだが
クールな鏡夜先輩が
Kyoya- senpai, why would
someone as cool as you are
どうしてこんなホスト部なんて 突拍子もない話に乗ったんですか
go in for something
as crazy as the Host Club?
Because it was so crazy.
突拍子もないからさ
"Two years previous-"
Back then, being born
the third Otori son as I was,
あの頃　鳳家の三男に生まれた俺は
I was about to embark on my
last spring in middle school.
中等部最後の春を迎えようとしていた
Kyoya- kun!
鏡夜君　鳳鏡夜君
Otori Kyoya- kun!
昨日　君のところの新病院完成記念にうちの父が出席したんだ
My father attended
the completion commemoration
for your folks' new hospital yesterday.
He was so surprised!
驚いてたよ
He said it was like a who's who
of faces from the top of every field!
各界トップの錚々たる顔ぶれだったって
My father said to be sure
to extend his regards.
父がくれぐれもよろしくって
This is the son of the chairman
of a major electronics maker.
これは大手電気メーカー会長の御曹司
Thank you. I hope you will
come with him to the next one.
ありがとう　次ぎはぜひ君も御一緒に
Otori- kun!
鳳君
We heard you were at the head
of our class again.
また学年首席だったって？
This is the son of a major
department store family.
これは大手デパートの息子
You've got the class chairmanship
locked up for 3rd Year, huh?
三年に上がっても　委員長は君で決まりだな
This is the youngest son
of a well-known member of the Diet.
これは有名代議士の末息子
Look, look, it's Otori- san!
見て見て　鳳さんよ
He looks so sharp today.
今日も素敵ね
He really does.
本当
Some frivolous-minded girls.
ミーハーな令嬢達
Otori- kun...
鳳君 今度　うちの山荘に遊びに来ないか
How about coming over
to my mountain villa sometime?
He is the son of a well-
known fund manager.
彼は有名なファンドマネジャーの息子だ
How about you guys, too?
皆もどう？
The stars are extraordinarily
pretty from there,
星がとっても綺麗でさ
and we even built
in a small observatory.
小さな天体観測所も作ったんだ
It's a villa that my father uses for
vacations, so we might see him there.
父が休暇に使う山荘だから顔を合わせるかもしれないけど
I don't really care about the stargazing...
天体観測はどうでもいいが
I look forward to it.
それは楽しみだな
... but I am very
interested in your father.
君のお父さんにはとても興味があるよ
"The Otoris' home"
My, my, my, Kyoya- san,
あらあらあら　鏡夜さん
you've decided to impose on their
mountain villa for such a reason?
そんな理由で山荘にお邪魔することにしたの？
"Fuyumi Otori (24), Kyoya's sister"
I'm not imposing. They are the ones
who wanted me to come over.
お邪魔じゃありませんよ
向こうだって僕に来てほしがってる
This is pure give-and-take.
純粋なギブアンドテークです
It's absolutely impure, isn't it?
そんなのしっかり不純じゃないの
Perhaps they purely do want you
to come look at the stars, Kyoya- san.
あちらは純粋に鏡夜さんと星を眺めたいのかもしれなくてよ
It's so romantic, isn't it? Strengthening
friendships under a starry sky?
ロマンチックじゃないの
星空の下　深まる友情
Sister Fuyumi, pardon me,
芙裕美姉さん　すみませんが
人のクローゼットを引っ掻き回さないでいただけますか
but could I ask you not to rummage
around in my closet drawers?
Oh, no, Kyoya- san, I thought I would
organize your clothes for you.
鏡夜さんのお洋服を整理して差し上げようと思ったのに…
It won't go back in...
入らないわ
Please let the help take care of that.
そういうことは使用人に任せてください
ねぇ　鏡夜さん
Say, Kyoya- san...
Father being as strict as he is,
お父様はあんなふうに厳しい方だから
maybe you have a hard time
under all the pressure,
プレッシャーを感じて大変かもしれないけど
but you are different
from your older brothers,
あなたはお兄様たちとは違うのだし
so maybe you could relax a little bit.
少しくらい気を抜いたっていいのよ
It's true, I will not be
succeeding the Otori family.
そう　僕が鳳を継ぐことはありません
I am not like my untroubled brothers,
who simply had to go along
約束されたルートに乗って　ただ上に行けばいい
on the route that they were promised,
and keep heading upward.
気楽な兄さん達とは違います
It's because I am the third
son that I cannot relax.
三男だからこそ気が抜けないんです
I will certainly fulfill
the expectations placed upon me,
かけられた期待には確実に応え
and yet always respect my brothers,
and never step too far forward.
しかし　必ず兄を立て　決して前には出すぎないこと
How far can I demonstrate my abilities,
三男という枠を超えずに　どこまで実力を発揮できるか
without exceeding the limits
of being "third son"?
Painting the perfect picture on a canvas
that has already been placed
最初から立派な額縁に入れられたキャンバスに完璧な絵を描く
inside a magnificent frame-
that is my task.
それが僕の仕事だ
Kyoya- san, you are so bright,
鏡夜さんは頭がいいから
you will accomplish everything
you ever do well,
全てを上手くこなしてしまうんでしょうけど…
but will you be happy with that?
でもそれで　楽しいの？
Whether I am happy or unhappy
楽しいとか楽しくないなんて関係ないですよ
has nothing to do with it.
My oldest brother had already
graduated from medical school,
上の兄はすでに医学部を卒業し
and was already in training
at the same hospital as my father
現在は父と同じ病院で後継者として修業中
as his successor.
My second brother
is still in medical school,
二番目の兄は医学部在学中で
and after graduating, he plans
to get an MBA, and support our brother.
卒業後はMBAを取得し　兄のサポートにあたる予定
And then, there's me, the third son.
そして　三男の俺は
Kyoya...
鏡夜
Today is when that son of Suou's
was going to transfer in, right?
例の須王の息子が転入してくるのは今日だったな
The Suou group and we have
done much business,
須王財閥とうちは昔から多くの仕事で関係が深い
going way back, and our ties run deep.
There is also much business
in which we compete with each other.
競合　敵対しているビジネスも多くある
Which is exactly why it would not hurt
to become good friends with him.
だからこそ　よい友人になっておいて損はない
Keep your friends close,
味方とは仲良くすべし
and keep your enemies closer.
敵とはもっと仲良くすべしだ
Yes, Father.
はい　お父さん
Keeping yourself at the head of
the class while you're in school
在学中の首席キープなどはお前の兄達もこなしてきたことだ
is an accomplishment that
your brothers have achieved.
You must know that it will take
more than that to satisfy me.
私がもうそれぐらいで満足しないことは
分かっているはずだな？
Yes, Father.
はい　お父さん
I had confidence
人を見抜くこと
that I could see through people,
but they could not see through me.
そして　人に見抜かれないことには自信があった
Whomever the son from
the Suou group's family might be,
須王財閥の息子がどんなやつでも
making friends with him
at least would be easy.
仲良くなるくらいは簡単だ
I would do all that my father wanted.
全ては父の望むままに
Suou Tamaki. The child that
the Suou chairman had overseas.
須王環
須王の会長が外国で生ませた子
離縁した本妻との間には子供がなく
Having no children with
his wife, now divorced,
the chairman took him in,
after much dismay.
悩んだ末に　会長は彼を引き取った
And his love child becomes
the heir to the Suou group overnight.
妾の子が一夜にして須王財閥の後継者か
何て運のいい奴だ
What a lucky guy he is.
Chairman, vice-chairman, come over here.
委員長　副委員長　こちらへ
Let me introduce you.
This is Suou Tamaki- kun.
紹介しましょう　須王環君です
Pleasure to meet you.
どうぞ　よろしく
Class chairman Otori Kyoya- kun
and vice-chairman Jonouchi Ayame- kun.
君だ
Your hair is so straight and pretty.
とってもまっすぐで綺麗な髪だね
I'm sure your heart must also be
as true and beautiful as your hair.
きっと君の心もこの髪のようにますっぐで美しいのだろうね
Cultural differences?
お国柄か
よろしく　鳳君
It's a pleasure, Otori- kun.
The pleasure is mine. If you like,
こちらこそ　よければ学院内を案内しようか
how about I show you around the school?
I'd be thrilled.
それは嬉しいな
Up ahead here is the west school building.
ここから先が西校舎だよ
The special classrooms
are all on the other side.
特別教室は全部この向こうなんだ
Oh, right. By the way, Otori- kun,
そうだ　ところで　鳳君
do you have a kotatsu at your house?
君の家にコタツはあるか
コタツだよ　いいよな　コタツ
A kotatsu! Kotatsu sure are great, huh?
Here in Japan, where you
have the charming culture
床に直に座り　日本ならではの微笑ましき文化
of sitting right on the floor.
I made up my mind to be sure to sit
under one, once I got to Japan.
日本に来たら　絶対入るって決めてたんだ
But we only have western rooms at my place.
でも　うちには洋間しかなくて
Ah, he's one of those. The sort,
common among foreigners,
ああ　あれか
外国人によくある日本文化憧れ系って奴
who is in love with Japanese culture.
Unfortunately, we don't have
any kotatsu at my place, either.
残念だけど　うちにもコタツはないんだ
We do have some Japanese rooms, though.
和室はあるんだけどね
What? Did I step on some
sort of land mine?
なんだ　何か地雷を踏んだか
I see. You don't have a kotatsu, then?
I'm sorry, Otori- kun.
そうか　ないのか　コタツ
ごめんよ　鳳君
"Air wall!!"
そうとは知らず　無神経なことを…
It was insensitive of me
to ask, without knowing.
The family relations at your home
aren't all that close, huh?
君の家は家族仲がうまくいっていないんだな？
No, it's okay, you don't have to hide it.
いや　いいんだ　隠さなくても
コタツというのは　日本の家族団欒の象徴というではないか
The kotatsu is the symbol of a happy
home life in Japan, is it not?
In Japan, you kick each
other's feet under the kotatsu
日本ではコタツの中で足をぶつけあって
in playful fighting, while
watching Costume Grand Prix,
軽い喧嘩をしながら　仮装大賞を見て
and building bonds of trust
among the family, right?
家族の信頼関係を構築するのだろう
Oh, right, and you can't leave
out the mandarin oranges!
そうだ　蜜柑も欠かしてはならないのだったな
でも　そっか　君んちにはないのか…
But, I guess, you don't have
that at your place, huh?
"Pitying eyes..."
"Somewhat irritated..."
Let's just put your mistaken
understanding aside for now.
間違った知識はひとまず置いておいて
If you like, I could put a kotatsu
in one of our Japanese rooms.
よければうちの和室にコタツを用意しようか
Thank you, Otori- kun!
ありがとう　鳳君
You're a good friend!
My best friend!
君は親友だ　大親友だ
Hey, I know! To make us closer,
あっ　そうだ　親しみをこめて
これからはファーストネームで呼ばせてもらっていいかな
- would you let me call you by
your first name from now on?
- Suou- kun, um...
- would you let me call you by
your first name from now on?
須王君　あのう…
ブラボー　鏡夜　モナ～ミ　　モナ～ミ
Bravo! Kyoya! Mon ami!
Mon ami! Yahoo!
My, my, my, Kyoya- san,
あらあらあら　鏡夜さん
you mean, best friends, in one day?
そんな一日で親友に？
He probably doesn't comprehend
the meaning of "best friend."
多分親友の意味を理解してないんですよ
日本語が堪能なんだかそうじゃないんだか
I'm not sure if he's really fluent
in Japanese, or if he isn't.
And, like I said, Sister Fuyumi,
って　だから　芙裕美姉さん
please don't go rummaging
around in my closet drawers.
人のクローゼットを引っ掻き回さないでください
Today, he drew me in to playing
everything at his pace.
今日はすっかり向こうのペースに引き込まれっぱなしだったな
Well, I am well aware now
that he is a fool.
まっ　奴がバカであることはよく分かった
Kyoya- san, there is too
much crammed in here.
鏡夜さん　詰め込みすぎよ
Once you pull something out,
it won't fit in again, you know.
一度出したら　もう収まらないじゃない
Like I said, please
don't take them out.
だから　出さないでください
Kyoya!
鏡夜　折り入って頼みがあるのだ
I need a special favor from you.
"Serious!!"
You see, I want to go to Kyoto.
実は　京都に行きたいのだ
I had forgotten about it
in my joy over the kotatsu,
コタツの喜びでうっかりしていたが
日本に来たら　先ず京都に行こうと決めていたのだ
but I made up my mind to go to Kyoto
first, once I got to Japan.
The Great Buddha at Nara,
奈良の大仏と
Goryoraku Park,
五稜郭と
some Shisa,
シーサーと
the Namahage,
ナマハゲを
見に行きたいのだ
I want to see them all!
None of those are in Kyoto.
それ　全部京都じゃないけど…
He's a bigger fool than I thought.
思った以上のバカだなぁ
All right. Well,
shall we see them in turns?
分かった　じゃ　順に回ろうか
First off, we'll go to Kyoto this weekend,
先ず　今週末は京都に行って
and the next extended holiday
we get, we'll go to Okinawa.
次の連休に沖縄に行こう
Thank you, Kyoya!
ありがとう　鏡夜
You are a god!
The great Buddha! Bravo!
君は神様だ　大仏さまだ
ブラボー　鏡夜　モナ～ミ　モナ～ミ　モナーミ
Kyoya! Mon ami! Mon ami!
Mon ami! Yahoo!
Again with the "mon ami."
またモナーミ
And the second day after I've met him,
I'm elevated to a deity?
出会って二日目にして神様に昇格か
"Kyoto"
It's like I can't get a grasp
on this guy, somehow.
なんだか　まるで勝手の掴めない奴だ
Before I knew it, he was
fitting in with the class...
いつの間にかクラスにもなじんでるし
Kyoya! I found a Namahage!
鏡夜　ナマハゲ発見
Namahage! Namahage...
ナマハゲ　ナマハゲ　ナマハゲ…
"Okinawa"
That's a Shisa.
それはシーサー
My, my, my, Kyoya- san,
あらあらあら　鏡夜さん
"Hokkaido"
I thought you were up this late studying,
こんな遅くまでお勉強かと思ったら
but what's this?
Sightseeing guides?
な～に　観光ガイド？
Oh, you're going to go to
Hokkaido next? That's nice.
へぇー　今度は北海道に行くの？
いいわね
でも　案内役なら運転手に頼めば…
But if you need a guide,
I'm sure if you ask the driver...
That won't do.
Not for that Suou Tamaki guy.
それじゃダメなんですよ
あの須王環という奴は
When we went to Kyoto,
he said he wanted to see
京都へ行ったら　まだ春だというのに
the Daimonji bonfire,
even though it's still spring,
大文字の送り火が見たいだの
and as we were eating
Okinawa soba noodles,
沖縄そばをたべながら
he suddenly said he wanted
to compare it to Shinshu soba.
突然信州そばと食べ比べてみたいだの
Then he said he wanted to have a dream
シーサーとナマハゲの夢の共演が見たいだの
co-starring a Shisa and a Namahage.
And then, after all of that...
そして　あげくの果てには…
I'm sorry for asking you
to indulge my capriciousness.
ごめんな　わがまま言って
You're right.
It's no use asking you, Kyoya.
そうだよな　鏡夜に言っても無駄だよな
Sorry. I've overestimated your abilities.
すまない　君の能力を過大評価しすぎていた
しかし　これで次の準備は万全です
But I will be fully prepared
for him this time!
I will respond to his every
whim when we are in Hokkaido!
北海道では　やつのあらゆる気まぐれに応えて見せますよ
え　北海道？
Huh? Hokkaido?
I understand that you want
to enjoy yourself to the fullest,
遊びたい盛りなのは分かるが
but this is the time when we should
be studying for tests, right?
試験に備えて勉強すべき時期だろう
Once the tests are over,
I'll play with you,
試験が終わったら遊んでやるから
but you should study a little, too.
お前も少しは勉強しろよ
My, my, my, Kyoya- san,
あらあらあら　鏡夜さん
what on earth is the matter?
一体何事ですの
That bastard!
あのヤロウ
I knew the guy was a fool,
バカだ　バカだ　とは思っていたが
but I had no idea he was
such a complete dumb ass!
あそこまでどうしようもない…
大バカヤロウだったとは！
"Tamaki Suou last week"
Next week, let's go to Hokkaido!
来週は北海道に行こう
Have I ever felt like slugging
someone as much as this before?
これほどまでに誰かを殴りたいと思ったことはあるか
No! Definitely not!
否　断じて否だ
Whoa, calm down. Despite everything,
he is the heir to the Suou family.
落ち着け　あれでも奴は須王の後継者
What good will it do to
get emotional about it?
感情的になってどうする
What Father is testing me
on is my ability to cope.
父から試されているのは俺の対応能力なのだ
Still, you bastard,
I won't forget this! Suou Tamaki,
しかし　あのヤロウ　覚えていやがれ
須王環　誰かコタツなど用意してやるものか
you expect me to get
a kotatsu ready for you!?
I was going to tell him
that if he can't stand him,
もし　嫌な相手なら　無理して付き合うことない
there's no reason for him to force
himself to hang around with him,
って言ってあげるつもりだったけど
but I've never seen Kyoya-san
enjoy himself so much.
こんなに楽しそうな鏡夜さん
初めて見たわ
"The next Sunday"
It's been a while since I've had
a day off without having him along.
奴の相手をしない休日は久しぶりだな
Your friend is here to see you.
お友達が見えてるわよ
My friend?
友達？
Beautiful, isn't it?
素敵ね　なんだか泣けてきちゃう
It's bringing me to tears.
Honestly, when I first
heard him play the piano,
正直　奴のピアノを始めて聞いたそのとき
I was astonished. Not because
my brothers were in tears,
俺は驚いたものだ
兄が涙ぐんでたからじゃない
but because, unwittingly...
unwittingly, for some reason,
不覚にも　不覚にも　俺自身なぜか泣けてきたからだ
I started weeping, too.
Sorry for just coming by
out of the blue like this.
悪いな　突然来てしまって
If that's how you feel, go home.
そう思うなら帰れ
What happened to studying for
your tests? You sure you're okay?
試験勉強はどうした　いいのか
I have to say, your house is huge, Kyoya.
しかし　広いな　鏡夜の家は
I wonder which is bigger, this,
or my house back in France.
俺の住んでたフランスの家とどっちが広いかなぁ
嫌味か
Snide remarks, now?
I don't know about your
mansion in France,
フランスのお屋敷は知らないが
but clearly, the Suou estate
is bigger, isn't it?
明らかに須王邸のほうが大きいだろう
Well, I don't know, since I've
never entered the main estate.
いや　俺は本邸には入ったことないから分からない
第二邸はもっと狭いよ
The second estate is much smaller.
So, Kyoya, are you going to take
over the Otori family later on?
それで　鳳家は将来鏡夜が継ぐのか
Is this guy trying to pick a fight!?
喧嘩売ってんのか　こいつ
There's no way I will. You saw that
I have two older brothers, right?
継ぐはずないだろ
見たろ　兄が二人いるのを
I will end up working under my brothers.
僕は兄の下で働くことになるんだ
Huh, that's a surprise.
あれ　それは意外
I thought you were someone
who wanted more than that.
君はもっと貪欲な人間かと思ってた
I mean, your eyes say
that you're completely
だって　現状に全然満足してないって目だろ　それ
unsatisfied with your situation
I'm surprised you're giving up so easily.
意外と諦めいいんだな
It's not a question of whether
I'm giving up or not...
諦めるとか諦めないとかの問題じゃない
It's just the way it is!
そう決まってるんだ
Someone like you,
君のように　当たり前な顔で家を継ぐ人間には分からないのかな
who is going to succeed their
family as a matter of course,
wouldn't understand.
Whoops...
しまった
俺は須王を継ぐとは決まってないぞ
It isn't certain that I will
succeed the Suou family.
My grandmother doesn't like me.
俺はお祖母様に嫌われてる
So, if it keeps going like this, they say
that I won't be the heir, or anything.
だから　今のままなら全然跡継ぎとかじゃないんだって
Call it a probationary period,
I guess. Didn't I ever tell you?
お試し期間っていうの
あれ　言わなかったっけ
Still, think about it. It's not like
I'm not interested in my father's work,
けど　考えてもみろ
父の仕事に興味がないわけじゃないが
but I've got these looks.
Those around me can't leave me alone.
この美貌だぞ
周りが放っておかないだろう
Maybe with my outstanding smarts,
I could be a brilliant scientist,
あるいはこの優秀な頭脳なら
天才科学者になるかもしれないし
and more than anything,
何より北の大地に動物王国とかも作ってみたいし
I'd love to create an animal
kingdom in the lands up north.
ふざけるな
Come off it!
What kind of bull crap is that?
何ふざけたこと言ってる
How can you talk like
you've given up so easily!?
なぜそんな簡単に諦めたようなことが言える
お前は俺とは違う
You aren't like me!
努力すればいくらでも上にいけるチャンスを手にしてるだろ
You have a chance to go as high
as you want to, if you'll just try!
だったら　なぜもっと努力をしない
So why don't you try harder!?
Why don't you use the position
you've been blessed with!?
なぜその恵まれた立場を利用しない
You're just... you're just...
お前は…お前は…
Who the hell are you!?
お前は一体なんなんだ
"You're such an idiot!
How can you see through me?"
Yeah... I'm sure that my brothers'
aptitudes are no better than mine.
そうさ　実力なら　兄にも負けない自信はある
だけど…
But...
But I will always feel the frustration
だけど三男というだけで
of not being allowed to exceed
my frame, just because...
越えることが許されない枠がある悔しさを
... I am the third son.
俺はいつだって…
Hold on, you're the one
who isn't trying, right?
なんだ　努力してないのはお前の方だろ
If you want to surpass your
brothers, then go ahead.
兄貴達を越えたきゃ越えればいい
何もしてないのに諦めてるのは　お前の方だ
The one who isn't doing anything,
and has given up here...
...is you.
By the way, Kyoya,
where is your kotatsu?
ところで　鏡夜
コタツはどこかな
The truth is, I thought you would
have gotten it ready for me by now,
実はそろそろ用意してくれたんじゃないかって思って
which is why I came over.
遊びに来たんだが
What? What's so funny?
なんだ　何がおかしい？
さてはコタツを用意しておいて　隠しているのか
Now, did you get the kotatsu ready,
and you're just hiding it from me?
Don't get so carried away!
調子にのるな
Kotatsu are only used in the winter.
コタツは冬と決まってる
If you want to sit under one,
wait until winter.
入りたければ冬まで待て
You big dumb ass.
この大バカヤロウが
おお～　悪そうな顔
Oh, that's an evil-looking face.
Is that what you really look like?
本当はそういう顔なのか
"Four months later-"
Kyoya, I just had an incredible idea!
鏡夜　すごいことを思い付いたぞ
Let's form a club!
部を立ち上げよう
We can start our activities as soon
as we get into the high school.
高等部に入ったら　すぐに活動開始だ
我々の美貌を生かした　その名も「ホスト部」
We'll make use of our good looks,
and call it the Host Club!
Go to sleep before you start dreaming.
寝言は寝て言え
I've thought about who
the other members would be.
他のメンバーも考えてある
Haninozuka- senpai and
Morinozuka- senpai, from high school,
高等部の埴之塚先輩に銛之塚先輩
and the twins from 2nd Year.
それと二年の双子な
The more I listened, the more
nonsensical his plans were.
聞けば聞くほどそれらはくだらない計画だった
But I got the feeling that
if I shared his world,
けれど　こいつの世界を共有したら
I would see something different
from anything I had seen before.
何かこれまでとは違う風景が
俺にも見えてくるような気がした
As a special event during
our school festival,
学祭スペシャルイベントとして
我がホスト部を公開する今日と明日のこの二日間
today and tomorrow, the Host Club
will be opened to the public.
We will entertain our guests
even more extravagantly,
いつも以上に華やかに咲き誇るように接客するのだ
and in full bloom than usual.
Next time,
"The Host Club Declares Dissolution"
Ouran High School Host Club
will be waiting for you, next week!
桜蘭高校ホストクラブ　来週も
お待ちしております